A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.33 (A2007) FA492
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.33 (A2007)
1978-2006
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA492
66.81 Cubic Feet 51 standard record storage boxes, R3826-R3837, R3837A, R3838-R3844, R3179A, R3846-R3864, R3864A, R3865-R3873,
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (digital media) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Scope and Contents
Contains grant administration files.
- AC.2007.001: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2004; AC.2007.001; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3826, R3827, R3829, R3831.
  - Health Equity (HE), AC.2007.001.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2001 HE 020 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - MEETING ON ROAD SAFETY IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2000-2003 (Box R3826)
    - 2001 HE 024 - INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL MEDICINE (BELGIUM) - MICROBICIDES 2002 CONFERENCE, 2000-2003 (Box R3826)
    - 2001 HE 028 - TELEVISION TRUST FOR THE ENVIRONMENT (ENGLAND) - TV SERIES ON HEALTH EQUITY, LIFE, 1999-2002 (Box R3826)
    - 2001 HE 029 - JOINT CLINICAL RESEARCH CENTRE (UGANDA) - MEETING ON AIDS CARE IN AFRICA, 2001-2003 (Box R3826)
    - 2001 HE 030 - INTER-AMERICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK - COALITION FOR THE PREVENTION OF VIOLENCE, 2001-2004 (Box R3826)
    - 2001 HE 036 - RAKS THAI FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - HIV PREVENTION IN THAILAND, MAYANMAR AND CAMBODIA, 2001-2003 (Box R3826)
    - 2001 HE 044 - NARESUAN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - BENCHMARKS OF FAIRNESS AND HEALTH DEVELOPMENT, 2001-2003 (Box R3826)
    - 2001 HE 048 - INDEPTH NETWORK (GHANA) - PLATFORM FOR HEALTH EQUITY RESEARCH, 2001-2002 (Box R3826)
    - 2001 HE 051 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - KNOWLEDGE RESOURCE CENTERS, 2001-2004 (Box R3826)
    - 2001 HE 051 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - KNOWLEDGE RESOURCE CENTERS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2001-2004 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 052 - GLOBAL NETWORK OF PEOPLE LIVING WITH AIDS (NETHERLANDS) - 10TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE IN TRINIDAD, 2001-2002 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 054 - COMMONWEALTH REGIONAL HEALTH COMMUNITY SECRETARIAT FOR EAST, CENTRAL, AND SOUTHERN AFRICA (TANZANIA) - REGIONAL CAPACITY-BUILDING WORKSHOP, 2001-2003 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 058 - GAY MEN'S HEALTH CRISIS - FORUM ON ANTIRETROVIRAL THERAPY IN THE DEVELOPING WORLD, 2001-2003 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 059 - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH MATTERS (ENGLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: IMPACT OF HEALTH SECTOR REFORM ON SEXUAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH POLICY AND SERVICES, 2000-2002 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 060 - GHANA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - ADOLESCENT SEXUAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 2001-2002 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 061 - INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION - BC CONFERENCE: FULBRIGHT NEW CENTURY SCHOLAR PROGRAM, 2001-2004 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 063 - MEDICAL RESEARCH COUNCIL (ENGLAND) - INTERNATIONAL WORKING GROUP ON MICROBICIDES, 2001-2004 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 070 - BURKINA FASO - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - XllTH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON AIDS AND STDs, 2001-2002 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 082 - INTERNATIONAL VACCINE INSTITUTE (SOUTH KOREA) - MEETING ON DENGUE VACCINE FOR CHILDREN, 2001-2003 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 087 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - GLOBAL CONFERENCE ON HEALTH EQUITY, 2001-2002 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 089 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN - MICROBICIDES ACCESS WORKING GROUP (CANCELLED), 2001-2002 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 090 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - SYMPOSIUM ON AIDS IN THE MEKONG REGION, 2001-2002 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 092 - HONG KONG TUBERCULOSIS, CHEST AND HEART DISEASES ASSOCIATION - ASIA PACIFIC CONFERENCE ON TOBACCO OR HEALTH, 2001-2002 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 094 - STATE FAMILY PLANNING COMMISSION (CHINA) - TRAINING ON REMOVAL OF SUB-DERMAL CONTRACEPTIVE IMPLANTS, 2001-2003 (Box R3827)
    - 2001 HE 099 - LAO P.D.R. - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - DENEGUE SURVEILLANCE, 2001-2002 (Box R3827)
  - Population and Cairo Agenda (PC), AC.2007.001.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 PC 020 - COUNCIL ON FOREIGN RELATIONS - WOMEN'S RIGHTS AND U.S. FOREIGN POLICY, 2000-2002 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PC 022 - UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - GENDER AND AGING IN ASIA, 2000-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PC 024 - HELPAGE INTERNATIONAL - DEMOGRAPHIC AGING ISSUES IN AFRICA, 2000-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PC 025 - WOMEN'S LAW AND PUBLIC POLICY FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM - SOUTH AFRICA AND WOMEN'S RIGHTS, 1999-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PC 028 - BOSTON WOMEN'S HEALTH BOOK COLLECTIVE - DIALOGUE ON WOMEN'S REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 2000-2002 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PC 029 - COALITION FOR WOMEN'S ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND GLOBAL EQUALITY - WOMEN AND GLOBALIZATION, 2000-2002 (Box R3829)
  - Program Venture Experiment (PV), AC.2007.001.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 PV 005 - UNITED NATIONS RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT (SWITZERLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: IMPROVING RESEARCH AND KNOWLEDGE ON SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT IN INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATIONS, 2000-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PV 006 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - RICKETS PREVENTION IN BANGLADESH, 2000-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PV 007 - SINGAMMA SREENIVASAN FOUNDATION (INDIA) - IMPROVE CONFERENCE FACILITIES, 2000-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PV 011 - AMERICAN UNIVERSITY IN CAIRO (EGYPT) - VISITING PROFESSORSHIP FOR ISMAIL SERAGELDIN, 2000-2002 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PV 019 - WILLIAM GREAVES PRODUCTIONS - DOCUMENTARY FILM ON RALPH BUNCHE, 2000-2003 (Box R3829)
  - Regional Nairobi (RN), AC.2007.001.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 RN 004 - LEGAL EDUCATION FOUNDATION (KENYA) - MECHANISMS OF CONFLICT PREVENTION AND RESOLUTION IN AFRICA, 1999-2002 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 RN 016 - BOSTON COLLEGE - ACADEMIC PROFESSION AND GLOBAL EDUCATION, 2000-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 RN 021 - DEVELOPMENT INNOVATIONS AND NETWORKS (ZIMBABWE) - SUMMIT ON MICROCREDIT IN AFRICA, 2000-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 RN 022 - YALE UNIVERSITY - SYMPOSIUM SERIES ON INTERNATIONAL HIGHER EDUCATION, 1999-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 RN 023 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - POVERTY MAPPING IN MALAWI AND MOZAMBIQUE, 2000-2003 (Box R3829)
  - Working Communities (WC), AC.2007.001.5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 WC 030 - CENTER ON POLICY INITIATIVES - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1992-2002 (Box R3831)
    - 2000 WC 041 - COMMUNITY PARTNERS - PROJECT FORUM ON RACE AND DEMOCRACY, 2000-2003 (Box R3831)
    - 2000 WC 062 - ASIAN PACIFIC AMERICAN LEGAL CENTER OF SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA, INC. - REDISTRICTING PROCESS FROM 2000 CENSUS AND CONSEQUENCES FOR ASIAN AMERICANS, 1998-2003 (Box R3831)
    - 2000 WC 062 - ASIAN PACIFIC AMERICAN LEGAL CENTER OF SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA, INC. - REDISTRICTING PROCESS FROM 2000 CENSUS AND CONSEQUENCES FOR ASIAN AMERICANS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2003 (Box R3831)
    - 2000 WC 063 - PHILANTHROPIC COLLABORATIVE - DEMOS PROJECT, 1999-2002 (Box R3831)
    - 2000 WC 066 - LAWYERS' COMMITTEE FOR CIVIL RIGHTS UNDER LAW - FAIR REDISTRICTING PROJECT, 1998-2003 (Box R3831)
    - 2000 WC 067 - PUERTO RICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATION FUND - CIVIC PARTICIPATION AND VOTING RIGHTS PROJECT, 2000-2003 (Box R3831)
    - 2000 WC 068 - MEXICAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - 2000-2001 REDISTRICTING PROJECT, 2000-2003 (Box R3831)
    - 2000 WC 068 - MEXICAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - 2000-2001 REDISTRICTING PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2000-2003 (Box R3831)
  - Special Programs (SP), AC.2007.001.6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 SP 220 - POPULATION AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (THAILAND) - GENERAL SUPPORT EMANATING FROM RF BOARD TRIP, 2000-2002 (Box R3831)
    - 2001 SP 333 - JSI RESEARCH TRAINING INSTITUTE, INC. - GLOBAL EQUITY AND SECURITY, 2001-2003 (Box R3831)
    - 2001 SP 503 - NATIONAL EMPLOYMENT LAW PROJECT - EMPLOYMENT NEEDS OF LOW-WAGE AND IMMIGRANT WORKERS AFFECTED BY THE WTC ATTACK, 2001-2003 (Box R3831)
    - 2001 SP 504 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION - SUPPORT FOR IMMIGRANT ACCESS PROJECT, 2001-2002 (Box R3831)
    - 2001 SP 505 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - ARTS REBUILDING INITIATIVE, 2001-2002 (Box R3831)
    - 2001 SP 506 - ISLAMIC CIRCLE OF NORTH AMERICA - 9/11: COMMUNITY-ORIENTED RESPONSE EFFORT, 2001-2004 (Box R3831)
    - 2001 SP 507 - ASIAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATION FUND - ANTI-VIOLENCE/EMERGENCY LEGAL RESPONSE PROJECT, 2001-2003 (Box R3831)
- AC.2007.002: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1999-2006; AC.2007.002; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3828 and R3830.
  - Population and Cairo Agenda (PC), AC.2007.002.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 PC 004 - POPULATION COUNCIL - URBAN HEALTH STUDY WITH NAIROBI CENTER, 1999-2003 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PC 009 - ALAN GUTTMACHER INSTITUTE - STD HIV STUDY IN FIVE COUNTRIES, 1999-2006 (Box R3829)
    - 2000 PC 019 - LIAISON CENTRE FOR MEDICAL WOMEN IN AFRICA (KENYA) - GENDER BIAS AND EFFECT ON HEALTH OF KENYAN WOMEN, 1999-2003 (Box R3829)
  - Health Equity (HE), AC.2007.002.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 HE 115 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - BC CONFERENCE: ACHIEVING HEALTH EQUITY THROUGH INTERVENTIONS AGAINST AIDS/HIV, MALARIA AND TUBERCULOSIS, 2001-2002 (Box R3828)
    - 2001 HE 127 - THAI RED CROSS SOCIETY - FIFTH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON HOME AND COMMUNITY CARE FOR PERSONS LIVING WITH HIV/AIDS, 2001-2002 (Box R3828)
    - 2001 HE 129 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN - PUBLICATIONS ON MICROBICIDES, 2001-2002 (Box R3828)
    - 2001 HE 135 - THAILAND - PUBLIC HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - MEETING ON EPIDEMIOLOGY OF DENGUE IN THE MEKONG BASIN, 2001-2002 (Box R3828)
    - 2001 HE 136 - SUSTAINABLE SCIENCES INSTITUTE - DENGUE TRAINING WORKSHOP IN ECUADOR, 2001-2002 (Box R3828)
    - 2002 HE 004 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA - FORUM ON POLIO ERADICATION (Box R3828)
    - 2002 HE 026 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - GLOBAL EQUITY GAUGE ALLIANCE, 2002-2004 (Box R3828)
    - 2002 HE 028 - GEORGE WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY - TRANSFER OF TECHNOLOGIES AND HIV/AIDS ANTl-RETROVIRAL THERAPY, 2002-2003 (Box R3828)
    - 2002 HE 029 - CENTER FOR HEALTH AND GENDER EQUITY - HEALTH SECTOR REFORM ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH IN INDIA AND TANZANIA, 2001-2004 (Box R3828)
    - 2002 HE 031 - MEDICAL RESEARCH COUNCIL, SOUTH AFRICA - MEETING TO SET GLOBAL TB RESEARCH PRIORITIES, 2002-2003 (Box R3828)
    - 2002 HE 040 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - MEETING ON SURVEILLANCE IN WEST AFRICA AND SUDAN (Box R3828)
    - 2002 HE 050 - TREATMENT ACTION CAMPAIGN (SOUTH AFRICA) - MEETING ON HIV/AIDS TREATMENT, 2002-2003 (Box R3828)
    - 2002 HE 059 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - FRENCH AND SPANISH EDITIONS OF MICROBICIDES REPORT, 2002-2003 (Box R3828)
    - 2002 HE 095 - NATIONAL HEALTH RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT CENTRE (KENYA) - WORKSHOP ON LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2002 (Box R3828)
  - RO, AC.2007.002.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 RO 001 - ESQUEL FOUNDATION (ECUADOR) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1994-2004 (Box R3830)
  - Southeast Asia (SE), AC.2007.002.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 SE 002 - KHON KAEN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - WORKSHOP ON NEEDS OF EDUCATIONAL INSTITUTIONS IN LAOS AND CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT IN THAI UNIVERSITIES, 2001-2002 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SE 012 - HUE UNIVERSITY (VIETNAM) - PARTICIPATION OF SCULPTORS AT THIRD INTERNATIONAL SCULPTURE SYMPOSIUM, 2001-2002 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SE 016 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - ATTENDANCE AT SOUTHEAST ASIA REGIONAL SCHOOL IN FORCED MIGRATION, 2001-2002 (Box R3830)
  - Special Programs (SP), AC.2007.002.5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 SP 102 - AFRICAN MEDICAL AND RESEARCH FOUNDATION (KENYA) - AFRIAFYA NETWORK, 2000-2002 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 104 - UNITED NATIONS POPULATION FUND - 2001 ROUNDTABLE ON DEVELOPMENT COMMUNICATION, 2001-2002 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 106 - SOUND PORTRAITS PRODUCTIONS - EXECUTION TAPES, 2001-2002 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 107 - BRITISH BROADCASTING CORP. (ENGLAND) - RADIO SERIES ON HISTORY OF AFRICA, 1999-2003 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 109 - POPULATION COMMUNICATIONS INTERNATIONAL - BROADCAST PROJECTS ON HIV/AIDS IN KENYA AND TANZANIA, 2001-2004 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 111 - KOAHNIC BROADCAST CORP. - NATIVE AMERICAN PROGRAMMING, 2001-2003 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 115 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR GLOBAL COMMUNICATIONS FOUNDATION - DOCUMENTARY, "SPEAK UP YOUNG AFRICA", 2001-2004 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 206 - WORLD AFFAIRS COUNCIL OF NORTHERN CALIFORNIA - CONFERENCE ON GIVING WITHOUT BORDERS, 2001-2002 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 207 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - CONFERENCE ON IMPACTS OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT, 2001-2003 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 209 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF PUBLIC HEALTH (MEXICO) - MEETING ON PAN-AMERICAN HEALTH IN THE 21ST CENTURY, 2001-2002 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 217 - UNITED NATIONS - MEETING TO ADVISE SECRETARY-GENERAL ON PRIORITY ISSUES, 2001-2003 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 218 - PHILANTHROPIC COLLABORATIVE, INC. - ENCOURAGING U.S. DONORS TO GIVE GLOBALLY, 2001-2004 (Box R3830)
    - 2001 SP 219 - ACTIONAID (ENGLAND) - PUBLICATION AND DISTRIBUTION OF "A BROKEN LANDSCAPE", 2001-2003 (Box R3830)
- AC.2007.004: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1996-2006; AC.2007,004; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3837, R3837A, R3838.
  - Working Communities (WC), AC.2007.004.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2000 WC 069 - NAACP LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - VOTING RIGHTS AND REDISTRICTING RELATED TO 2000 CENSUS, 1999-2004 (Box R3837)
    - 2000 WC 070 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN (MADISON) - RESTRUCTURING OF HOTELS AND THE ROLES OF INSTITUTIONS, 2000-2002 (Box R3837)
    - 2000 WC 094 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - COMMUNITY BUILDING THEORETICAL AND CASE STUDIES, 2000-2003 (Box R3837)
    - 2000 WC 103 - DEVELOPMENT TRAINING INSTITUTE - HUMAN CAPITAL DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2003 (Box R3837)
    - 2000 WC 110 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - INTERNATIONAL CONTINGENT WORK MEETING, 2002 (Box R3837)
    - 2000 WC 129 - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS (AUSTIN) - LABOR MARKET INTERMEDIARIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3837)
    - 2000 WC 135 - OFFICE OF THE UNITED NATIONS HIGH COMMISSIONER FOR HUMAN RIGHTS (SWITZERLAND) - RACISM CONFERENCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 003 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT FELLOWSHIPS, 2000-2004 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 010 - SAN FRANCISCO LEAGUE OF URBAN GARDENERS - SOUTHEAST NEIGHBORHOOD JOBS INITIATIVE ROUNDTABLE, 2000-2004 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 014 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - OUTREACH PLAN FOR PHILANTHROPIC COLLABORATIVE, 2002 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 015 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - IMPLEMENTATION OF REPORT, "SUSTAINING THE STRUGGLE FOR JUSTICE", 1997-2002 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 015 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - IMPLEMENTATION OF REPORT, "SUSTAINING THE STRUGGLE FOR JUSTICE" - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (TRANSCRIPTS), 1997-2002 (Box R3837A)
    - 2001 WC 016 - LAWYERS' COMMITTEE FOR CIVIL RIGHTS UNDER LAW - DEVELOP NEW MECHANISMS FOR EXPANDING ITS FUNDING BASE, 2001-2003 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 021 - ASIAN PACIFIC AMERICAN LEGAL CENTER OF SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA - PROJECT FORUM ON RACE AND DEMOCRACY, 2001-2004 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 027 - CITYSKILLS - PIPELINE PROJECT, 2001-2004 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 030 - COUNCIL OF COMMUNITY SERVICES - WORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT CAPACITY BUILDING, 2000-2005 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 033 - GREATER BALTIMORE ALLIANCE FOUNDATION - WORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT ALLIANCE, 2001-2002 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 036 - NORTHLAND INSTITUTE - NATIONAL GATHERING OF SOCIAL ENTREPRENEURS, 2000-2002 (Box R3837)
    - 2001 WC 043 - MAKE THE ROAD BY WALKING - WORKPLACE JUSTICE PROJECT, 2001-2002 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 046 - INTER-AMERICAN DIALOGUE - INTER-AGENCY CONSULTATION ON RACE IN LATIN AMERICA, 2001-2003 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 052 - INTERNATIONAL HUMAN RIGHTS LAW GROUP - WORLD CONFERENCE ON RACISM, XENOPHOBIA AND OTHER FORMS OF INTOLERANCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 053 - SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA ASSOCIATION FOR PHILANTHROPY - LOS ANGELES URBAN FUNDERS CONSORTIUM, 1999-2004 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 060 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - ECONOMIC STIMULUS PLAN FOR WORKING FAMILIES, 2001-2002 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 063 - INSTITUTE FOR WISCONSIN'S FUTURE, INC. - WORKING FAMILIES ORGANIZING PROJECT, 2001-2002 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 065 - JUST ECONOMICS - LINKING RESEARCH AND ORGANIZING THROUGH ECONOMIC EDUCATION, 2001-2006 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 072 - VELASQUEZ INSTITUTE - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1999-2003 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 073 - BAY AREA INSTITUTE - CROSS-CULTURAL COMMUNICATIONS PROJECT, 1996-2004 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 080 - PROGRESSIVE, INC. - "VOICES OF DIVERSITY" SERIES, 2001-2002 (Box R3838)
    - 2001 WC 081 - UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS - RACE AND NATION IN THE GLOBAL SOUTH INITIATIVE, 1999-2003 (Box R3838)
- AC.2007.007: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1999-2006; AC.2007.007; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, R3832-R3836.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RESIDENT (Alexander, Victoria N.) (CO-RESIDENT: Crutchfield, James P.), 2000-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Alpers, Paul), 2000-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Altieri, Miguel A.), 1999-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Austin, Elizabeth R.), 2001-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Beisel, Nicola K.), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Benjamin, Marina), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Berger, Harry), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Bergmarm, Bettina), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Berlin, Normand), 2000-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Bidegain Greising, Ana M.) (CO-RESIDENT: LaRosa, Michael), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Blasius, Mark), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Bodemann, Y. Michal), 1999-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Boone, John), 2000-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Brooke, Nicholas J.), 2000-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Brown, Elizabeth), 2000-2003 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Calvert, Bruce) (CO-RESIDENT: Marinov, Corneliu), 1999-2004 (Box R3832)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Open in 2025
    - RESIDENT (Carroll, Jackson W.) (CO-RESIDENT: Roof, Wade Clark), 2000-2006 (Box R3832)
      Restricted - Open in 2027
    - RESIDENT (Charon, Rita), 1999-2006 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Chen, Shih-Hui), 2001-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Childers, Mary M.), 2000-2005 (Box R3832)
      Restricted - Open in 2026
    - RESIDENT (Christ, Carol T.), 2000-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Clancy, Patrick), 2000-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Clark, Emilie), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Clement, Wallace), 2000-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Cohen, Warren I.), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Cribb, Julian H. J.) (CO-RESIDENT: Hartomo, Endang T.S.), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Cuban, Lany), 2000-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Curthoys, Ann) (CO-RESIDENT: Docker, John E.), 1999-2001 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Daiute, Colette), 2000-2006 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (Davis, Adrienne Dale), 2000-2002 (Box R3832)
    - RESIDENT (de Obschatko, Edith S.), 2000-2005 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Del Tredici, David), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Dennett, Daniel C.), 2000-2003 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Doati, Roberto), 1999-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Dobronravin, Nikolai), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Driscoll, Ellen), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Evenson, Robert), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Fain, Gordon), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Faludi, Andreas), 2000-2002 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Feinstein, Rochelle H.), 1999-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Frank, Roberta), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Frantzen, Allen J.), 2001-2004 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Gal, Allon), 1999-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Garcia Ramis, Magali), 2001-2002 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Gillam, Barbara Jean), 2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Gillespie, Alexander Mathew), 2001-2002 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Gilson, Lucy Jennifer) (CO-RESIDENT: Walt, Gill), 2000-2003 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Goffart, Walter Andre), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Gontarski, Stanley E.), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Gruen, Erich S.), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Gubar, Susan), 2000-2003 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Halpern, Charles R.), 2000-2004 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Hammer, Barbara), 2000-2004 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Haney Lopez, Ian F.), 2000-2002 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Hargreaves, Andy), 2000-2004 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Hariharan, Githa), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Hartman, Saidiya V.), 2000-2002 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Haven, Jing J ing Luo), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Headings, Verle E.), 2000-2001 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Hoagland, Edward), 1999-2002 (Box R3833)
    - RESIDENT (Hyla, Lee), 2000-2002 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Iimura, Takahiko), 2000-2002 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Isaacman, Allen), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Ishiyama, Fumihiko) (CO-RESIDENT: Morigiwa, Yasutomo), 2000-2002 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Jehenson, Myriam Y.) (CO-RESIDENT: Dunn, Peter N.), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Johnson, Jeffrey Allan) (CO-RESIDENT: MacLeod, Roy Malcolm), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Jones, John Richard William Day), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Juan, Anthony Manavis), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Kahler, Miles), 2000-2002 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Keeton, Darra), 1999-2002 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Keller, Evelyn Fox), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Kenny, Nuala Patricia), 2000-2003 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Lapidoth, Amos), 2000-2004 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (LeBaron, Anne), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Levy, Frank), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Lomsky-Feder, Edna) (CO-RESIDENT: Rapoport, Tamar), 2001-2002 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Lowry, Beverly), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Lukow, Pawel), 2000-2002 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Magueijo, Joao), 2000-2003 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Maniere, Philippe), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Maxwell, David James), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (McDonough, Joyce M.), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (McDowell) (CO-RESIDENT: Richmond, Wendy), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Merson, Michael H.), 2001-2002 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Mihaila, Rodica), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Muller, Jerry Z.), 2000-2001 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Muller, Wolfgang C.) (CO-RESIDENT: Strom, Kaare), 2000-2004 (Box R3834)
    - RESIDENT (Muranyi, Miklos), 2000-2005 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Naksorn, Archan) (CO-RESIDENT: Siributr, Jakkai), 2000-2002 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Nauenberg, Michael), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Nickelsburg, George W. E.), 2000-2003 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Nuthall, Graham), 2000-2002 (Box R3835)